
export const dataLevels = [



    {
        id:1,
      title: "Beginner lvl Qestion 1",
      question:'Which unit is more powerful?',
      answer: [`Archangel`, `Black Dragon`, `Titan`, `Lazure Dragon`],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      level: 'begginer',

    },

    {
      id:2,
      title: "Qestion 2",
      question: 'How many gold/day gives you  a capitol?',
      answer: [`3000`, `5000`, `4000`, `40000,`],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      level: 'begginer',

    },
    { id:3,
      title: "Qestion 3",
      question: 'Chose the name of heroe, who have default spell - lightning chain?',
      answer: [`Sandro`, `Solmir`, `Xeron`, `Jog,`],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      level: 'begginer',
    },
    {
      id:4,
      title: "Qestion 4",
      question: 'Which "Town" gives you ability to have a double-mana?',
      answer: [`Tower`, `Castle`, `Dungen`, `Inferno,`],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      level: 'begginer',
    },
    {
      id:5,
      title: "Qestion 5",
      question: 'How many items you need to combine a Statue of Legion?',
      answer: [`5`, `6`, `7`, `4,`],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      level: 'begginer',
    },
    {
      id:6,
      title: "Qestion 6",
      question: 'Which artifacte gives you "explosion" spell into your spellbock?',
      answer: [`Wizard's Well`, `Crown of Dragontooth`, `Helm of Chaos`, `Spellbinder's Hat`],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      level: 'begginer',
    },
    {
      title: "END QIUZ",
      question: '',

    },

  {
      id:7,
      title: "Middle lvl Qestion 1",
      question: 'Which unit is more powerful?',
      answer: [`Archangel`, `Black Dragon`, `Titan`, `Lazure Dragon`],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      level: 'begginer',
  },
  {
      id:8,
      title: "Qestion 2",
      question: 'How many gold/day gives you  a capitol?',
      answer: [`3000`, `5000`, `4000`, `40000,`],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      level: 'begginer',

  },
  { id:9,
      title: "Qestion 3",
      question: 'Chose the name of heroe, who have default spell - lightning chain?',
      answer: [`Sandro`, `Solmir`, `Xeron`, `Jog,`],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      level: 'begginer',
  },
  {
      id:10,
      title: "Qestion 4",
      question: 'Which "Town" gives you ability to have a double-mana?',
      answer: [`Tower`, `Castle`, `Dungen`, `Inferno,`],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      level: 'begginer',
  },
  {
      id:11,
      title: "Qestion 5",
      question: 'How many items you need to combine a Statue of Legion?',
      answer: [`5`, `6`, `7`, `4,`],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      level: 'begginer',
  },
  {
      id:12,
      title: "Qestion 6",
      question: 'Which artifacte gives you "explosion" spell into your spellbock?',
      answer: [`Wizard's Well`, `Crown of Dragontooth`, `Helm of Chaos`, `Spellbinder's Hat`],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      level: 'begginer',
  },
  {
      title: "END QIUZ",
      question: '',

  },
  {
      id:13,
      title: "Master lvl Qestion 1",
      question:'Which unit is more powerful?',
      answer: [`Archangel`, `Black Dragon`, `Titan`, `Lazure Dragon`],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      level: 'begginer',

  },

  {
      id:14,
      title: "Qestion 2",
      question: 'How many gold/day gives you  a capitol?',
      answer: [`3000`, `5000`, `4000`, `40000,`],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      level: 'begginer',

  },
  { id:15,
      title: "Qestion 3",
      question: 'Chose the name of heroe, who have default spell - lightning chain?',
      answer: [`Sandro`, `Solmir`, `Xeron`, `Jog,`],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      level: 'begginer',
  },
  {
      id:16,
      title: "Qestion 4",
      question: 'Which "Town" gives you ability to have a double-mana?',
      answer: [`Tower`, `Castle`, `Dungen`, `Inferno,`],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      level: 'begginer',
  },
  {
      id:17,
      title: "Qestion 5",
      question: 'How many items you need to combine a Statue of Legion?',
      answer: [`5`, `6`, `7`, `4,`],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      level: 'begginer',
  },
  {
      id:18,
      title: "Qestion 6",
      question: 'Which artifacte gives you "explosion" spell into your spellbock?',
      answer: [`Wizard's Well`, `Crown of Dragontooth`, `Helm of Chaos`, `Spellbinder's Hat`],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      level: 'begginer',
  },
  {
      title: "END QIUZ",
      question: '',

  },

  {
      id:19,
      title: "Hardcore lvl Qestion 1",
      question: 'Which unit is more powerful?',
      answer: [`Archangel`, `Black Dragon`, `Titan`, `Lazure Dragon`],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      level: 'begginer',
  },
  {
      id:20,
      title: "Qestion 2",
      question: 'How many gold/day gives you  a capitol?',
      answer: [`3000`, `5000`, `4000`, `40000,`],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      level: 'begginer',

  },
  { id:21,
      title: "Qestion 3",
      question: 'Chose the name of heroe, who have default spell - lightning chain?',
      answer: [`Sandro`, `Solmir`, `Xeron`, `Jog,`],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      level: 'begginer',
  },
  {
      id:22,
      title: "Qestion 4",
      question: 'Which "Town" gives you ability to have a double-mana?',
      answer: [`Tower`, `Castle`, `Dungen`, `Inferno,`],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      level: 'begginer',
  },
  {
      id:23,
      title: "Qestion 5",
      question: 'How many items you need to combine a Statue of Legion?',
      answer: [`5`, `6`, `7`, `4,`],
      correctAnswer: 0,
      level: 'begginer',
  },
  {
      id:24,
      title: "Qestion 6",
      question: 'Which artifacte gives you "explosion" spell into your spellbock?',
      answer: [`Wizard's Well`, `Crown of Dragontooth`, `Helm of Chaos`, `Spellbinder's Hat`],
      correctAnswer: 3,
      level: 'begginer',
  },
  {
      title: "END QIUZ",
      question: '',

  },
  ]
